{
    "subject": "resource/Ian_Bruce_Ferguson",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/name",
    "object": "Ferguson, Ian",
    "human_readable": "The name of Ian Bruce Ferguson is Ferguson, Ian.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9695755839347839,
            "question": "Is 'Ferguson' Ian Bruce Ferguson's given name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9456369280815125,
            "question": "What is the middle name of Ian Bruce Ferguson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9378519058227539,
            "question": "What is Ian Bruce Ferguson's last name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9139761924743652,
            "question": "What is Ian Bruce Ferguson's first name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9099167585372925,
            "question": "What is the order of Ian Bruce Ferguson's names?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8884232640266418,
            "question": "Which part of Ian Bruce Ferguson's name comes first?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8533994555473328,
            "question": "If you were addressing Ian Bruce Ferguson formally, which part of his name would you use?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8291951417922974,
            "question": "What two parts make up Ian Bruce Ferguson's full name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8216599822044373,
            "question": "If you were to introduce Ian Bruce Ferguson, what name would you use first?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7013203501701355,
            "question": "How would you write Ian Bruce Ferguson's full name in reverse order?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of Ian Bruce Ferguson is Ferguson, Ian.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4761_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If you were to introduce Ian Bruce Ferguson, what name would you use first?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4761_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What two parts make up Ian Bruce Ferguson's full name?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4761_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If you were addressing Ian Bruce Ferguson formally, which part of his name would you use?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4761_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4761_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4761_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4761_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4761_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4761_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4761_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4761_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4761_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4761_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4761_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other triples to evaluate!  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information provided, I conclude that:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThis is because all the documents mention \"Ian Bruce Ferguson\" as a person with the last name Ferguson."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide sufficient information to support that the full name of the individual being discussed is indeed \"Ian Bruce Ferguson,\" with \"Ferguson\" as part of his surname and \"Bruce\" being a middle name."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Ferguson, Ian is not the full name of Ian Bruce Ferguson. He is known as Ian Bruce Ferguson.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided text consistently refers to him as \"Ian Bruce Ferguson\"  with his first name being Ian and his surname being Ferguson.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The claim is wrong because the name \"Ferguson\" appears to be a surname rather than a given name.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The name given in the context is \"Ian Bruce Ferguson,\" not \"Ferguson, Ian.\" The order of first and middle names is reversed in the statement.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}